fashionbunker.com 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy - BNKR

At BNKR, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and site visitors. BNKR team members are all customers themselves, of BNKR and other online stores, so we understand how important it is to keep your information secure and protected. 

Any personal information you provide to us will only be used to provide a service to you, or to improve your site experience. We will only use your personal information for the intended purpose, and we will not share or sell this personal information with any other organisations without your consent.However, as set out in this notice, we may disclose information to our service providers who assist in creating the best BNKR experience for you.

If you have any questions about your information or wish to have any of it deleted, please do not hesitate to contact customer service at [support@bnkr-store.com](mailto:support@bnkr-store.com).

### Your information + how we use it

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register an account on BNKR, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or enter a competition. This information includes: your name, email address, date of birth, shipping and billing addresses, phone number and payment information. 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company without your consent, for any reason other than the express purpose of delivering the product or service requested.

**What do we use your information for?**

We use your name, email, shipping and billing addresses and payment information to process and deliver your orders, as well as to provide any refunds or credits if you return your items.

We use your email address to send you updates about any orders you've placed, and we will only send you newsletters and promotional material if you give us permission by signing up.

If you choose to provide us with your date of birth, we use it to send you birthday offers and promotions. You can unsubscribe from our newsletter and promotional emails at any time, by using the 'Unsubscribe' link at the bottom of all emails or by contacting customer service at [support@bnkr-store.com](mailto:support@bnkr-store.com).

In addition to using your information to process, deliver and inform you about your purchases, we may also use it to personalise and improve your experience on BNKR, or to keep you up to date with our latest arrivals and promotions by showing you BNKR advertisements as you browse the web.

Your contact history, via email, telephone or livechat, may be used to provide you with the best customer service and to improve your BNKR experience.

Your purchase history and any items you have saved or viewed on BNKR may be used to gauge your product preferences, so we can deliver you the most relevant information and updates as well as the great customer service that you expect from BNKR.

Information provided in response to surveys, competitions or promotions will be used to fulfil the conditions of the offer or to improve your experience on BNKR.

### Sharing your information

**Do we share your information?**

****Your data will only be shared with trusted third parties who assist us in delivering a service to you, conducting our business or operating our website, that fall under the below categories:

  * Companies in the Australian Fashion Labels group, as sometimes different parts of our group are responsible for different activities
  * Companies that do things to get your orders to you, such as payment service providers, warehouses, order packers and delivery companies
  * Professional service providers, such as marketing agencies, advertising partners and website hosts, who help us run BNKR

We will only provide your information to companies that have agreed to strict confidentiality.

Outside of such third parties, BNKR does not and will never sell, trade or transfer your personally identifiable information. We may provide other parties with aggregated data that is anonymous and non-personally identifiable for marketing, analytics or other purposes. In addition to this, we may release your information when appropriate in order to comply with the law or to protect the rights, property or safety of others.

### Seeing BNKR advertisements online

**Why do I see BNKR advertisements while browsing online?**

We engage in online advertising to keep you aware of what is happening on BNKR and to help you see and find our products. Like many companies, we target BNKR banners and advertisements to you when you are on other websites and apps. This is done using a variety of digital marketing networks and ad exchanges, plus a range of technologies like pixels, ad tags, cookies, mobile identifiers, and services offered by some sites and social networks (such as Facebook). The banners and advertisements you see will be based on information we have about you, your BNKR browsing history or your interactions with previous BNKR advertisements.

### Cookies

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes, we do use cookies when you browse BNKR. Cookies are small files that a site or service provider transfers to your computer via your web browser, that enable us or our service providers to recognise your browser and/or capture certain information. We use cookies for a number of reasons:

  * To remember and process items in your shopping cart; so, for example, you can put items in your cart and come back and purchase them at a more convenient time
  * To understand and save your site preferences; to improve your future visits to BNKR
  * To keep track of advertisements; to ensure you are getting the most relevant advertising and to help us measure marketing campaigns
  * To compile aggregate data about site traffic and and interactions; to improve site functionality and your shopping experience

At times, we may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use any information collected on our behalf, except to help us conduct and improve our business.

By using our site, you agree to us placing these sorts of cookies on your device and accessing them when you visit BNKR in the future. If you prefer, you can choose to have your device warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can elect to disable all cookies or delete any cookies already sent. These preferences can be adjusted in your internet browser settings. Please note that, as with most websites, your user experience may be affected and you may not be able to take advantage of certain functions of our site. If you are having trouble placing orders, please contact customer care at [support@bnkr-store.com](mailto:support@bnkr-store.com). You can learn more about the cookies that we use [here](https://fashionbunker.com/cookies).

### Keeping your information + your rights

**Do we keep your information?**

We will hold on to your account information for as long as you have a BNKR account or as long as it is needed to provide our services to you. Outside of these circumstances, we may continue to hold your information if it is reasonably necessary to meet legal requirements, resolve payment disputes, prevent fraud or enforce our terms and conditions.

We do keep non-personally identifiable information, such as that gathered using cookies, for analytics purposes. You can disable cookies via your browser settings and read more about our use of cookies [here](https://fashionbunker.com/cookies).

**What rights do you have when it comes to your information?**

You have several rights regarding your personal information:

  * To be informed about how your personal information is being used (like this privacy notice)
  * To request and receive access to the personal information we have about you
  * To request the correction of any incorrect or inaccurate information we have about you
  * To request that we stop collecting or processing your data, and/or that we delete it
  * To stop receiving marketing messages, which you can do using the 'Unsubscribe' feature in such messages or by contacting [support@bnkr-store.com](mailto:support@bnkr-store.com)
  * To request that part or all of your data is transferred, either to you or to another service provider
  * To complain to your country's data protection regulator

If you wish to exercise these rights, to delete your account, or you have any questions or complaints, please do not hesitate to contact us at [support@bnkr-store.com](mailto:support@bnkr-store.com).

### Protecting your information

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into the database of our payment service provider. It is only accessible to those authorised with special access rights to such systems. Those with access to this information are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. If you elect to save your payment details for future orders, this information will be stored securely with our payment service provider.

### Terms and conditions + your consent

**Terms and Conditions**

We welcome you to also visit our Terms and Conditions page [here](https://fashionbunker.com/terms-conditions), which establishes the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline, for example in retail stores.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to this privacy policy and to our general [terms and conditions](https://fashionbunker.com/terms-conditions).

### Updates to the privacy policy

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be updated on this page. Major changes will be communicated, either by on site messaging or via email, so that you may review them before you continue using BNKR.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or your information, we invite you to contact us using the information below. 

BNKR

https://fashionbunker.com

Level 1, 233 North Terrace  
Adelaide, SA 5000  
Australia

08 70096000
